<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>About on Max Tacker's Personal Site</title><link>https://tacker.co/tags/about/</link><description>Recent content in About on Max Tacker's Personal Site</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://tacker.co/tags/about/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Goals for the Site</title><link>https://tacker.co/p/goals-for-the-site/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tacker.co/p/goals-for-the-site/</guid><description>&lt;img src="https://tacker.co/p/goals-for-the-site/image1.jpg" alt="Featured image of post Goals for the Site" />&lt;p>This article describes my personal goals for this site. These goals revolve around tech, software and hardware development, gardening, and my other interests.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="blog">Blog
&lt;/h2>&lt;p>The following HTML &lt;code>&amp;lt;h1&amp;gt;&lt;/code>—&lt;code>&amp;lt;h6&amp;gt;&lt;/code> elements represent six levels of section headings. &lt;code>&amp;lt;h1&amp;gt;&lt;/code> is the highest section level while &lt;code>&amp;lt;h6&amp;gt;&lt;/code> is the lowest.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="cv">CV
&lt;/h2>&lt;p>Xerum, quo qui aut unt expliquam qui dolut labo. Aque venitatiusda cum, voluptionse latur sitiae dolessi aut parist aut dollo enim qui voluptate ma dolestendit peritin re plis aut quas inctum laceat est volestemque commosa as cus endigna tectur, offic to cor sequas etum rerum idem sintibus eiur? Quianimin porecus evelectur, cum que nis nust voloribus ratem aut omnimi, sitatur? Quiatem. Nam, omnis sum am facea corem alique molestrunt et eos evelece arcillit ut aut eos eos nus, sin conecerem erum fuga. Ri oditatquam, ad quibus unda veliamenimin cusam et facea ipsamus es exerum sitate dolores editium rerore eost, temped molorro ratiae volorro te reribus dolorer sperchicium faceata tiustia prat.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Itatur? Quiatae cullecum rem ent aut odis in re eossequodi nonsequ idebis ne sapicia is sinveli squiatum, core et que aut hariosam ex eat.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="projects">Projects
&lt;/h2>&lt;p>The blockquote element represents content that is quoted from another source, optionally with a citation which must be within a &lt;code>footer&lt;/code> or &lt;code>cite&lt;/code> element, and optionally with in-line changes such as annotations and abbreviations.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="me">Me
&lt;/h2>&lt;p>![Image 1] (image1.jpg)&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>